const musicQuestions = {
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which Canadian reggae musician had a 1993 hit with the song 'Informer'?",
      "correct_answer": "Snow",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Rain",
        "Hail",
        "Sleet"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who had a 1983 hit with the song 'Africa'?",
      "correct_answer": "Toto",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Foreigner",
        "Steely Dan",
        "Journey"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "How many studio albums have the duo Daft Punk released?",
      "correct_answer": "4",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "1",
        "5",
        "2"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What was Rage Against the Machine's debut album?",
      "correct_answer": "Rage Against the Machine",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Evil Empire",
        "Bombtrack",
        "The Battle Of Los Angeles"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which one of these songs did the group 'Men At Work' NOT make?",
      "correct_answer": "Safety Dance",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Down Under",
        "Who Can It Be Now?",
        "It's a Mistake"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Kanye West at 2009 VMA's interrupted which celebrity?",
      "correct_answer": "Taylor Swift",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "MF DOOM",
        "Beyonce",
        "Beck"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "From which country did the song 'Gangnam Style' originate from?",
      "correct_answer": "South Korea",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Japan",
        "North Korea",
        "China"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which 80s band is fronted by singer/guitarist Robert Smith?",
      "correct_answer": "The Cure",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The Smiths",
        "Echo &amp; the Bunnymen",
        "New Order"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who was featured in the song 'Words' by Feint? ",
      "correct_answer": "Laura Brehm",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Anna Yvette ",
        "Danyka Nadeau",
        "Veela"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What was Daft Punk's first studio album?",
      "correct_answer": "Homework",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Discovery",
        "Random Access Memories",
        "Human After All"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who is the lead singer of Green Day?",
      "correct_answer": "Billie Joe Armstrong",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Mike Dirnt",
        "Sean Hughes",
        "Tr&eacute; Cool"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "'The Singing Cowboy' Gene Autry is credited with the first recording for all but which classic Christmas jingle?",
      "correct_answer": "White Christmas",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Frosty the Snowman",
        "Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer",
        "Here Comes Santa Claus"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which classical composer wrote the 'Moonlight Sonata'?",
      "correct_answer": "Ludvig Van Beethoven",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Chief Keef",
        "Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart",
        "Johannes Brahms"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which group performs the song 'Crash into Me'?",
      "correct_answer": "Dave Matthews Band",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Phish",
        "The Grateful Dead",
        "Destiny's Child"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "'Doctor Jones', 'Turn Back Time' and 'Barbie Girl' were UK number ones for which Eurodance group?",
      "correct_answer": "Aqua",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Vengaboys",
        "Eiffel 65",
        "Sash!"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What 1970's American ballad referred to the 1959 plane crash as the 'the day the music died'?",
      "correct_answer": "American Pie",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Kentucky Rain",
        "I Will Always Love You",
        "Rock 'n' Roll Suicide"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which punk rock band released hit songs such as 'Californication', 'Can't Stop' and 'Under the Bridge'?",
      "correct_answer": "Red Hot Chilli Peppers",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Green Day",
        "Linkin Park",
        "Foo Fighters"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "How many strings are there on a cello?",
      "correct_answer": "4",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "5",
        "6",
        "8"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which music publication is often abbreviated to NME?",
      "correct_answer": "New Musical Express",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "New Metro Entertainment",
        "Next Musical Enterprise",
        "North Manchester Express"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "'Hallelujah' is a song written by which Canadian recording artist?",
      "correct_answer": "Leonard Cohen",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Kory Lefkowits",
        "Ryan Letourneau ",
        "Justin Bieber "
      ]
    }
  ]
}

export default musicQuestions;